{
    "id": "c6743795fc59477ea1f95568f7e881e9",
    "title": "General English Exercise 1",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "a9d00b3a530e45daac4df04789e91879",
            "title": "General English Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He distributed the sweets ………………… .. the children.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "between",
                        "within",
                        "among"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which of the following words means the opposite of the word ‘generous’?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "foolish",
                        "lavish",
                        "dull",
                        "economical"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "Neither of them ………………….. fit for the job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are",
                        "could"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘This building is very old,’ the postmaster said. ‘I have to find an ………………… . building for the post office.’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "alternative",
                        "alternate",
                        "alternant"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "When I met her, she ………………… .. as a lecturer in a college.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was working",
                        "has been working",
                        "is working"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The sentence ‘Had I worked harder, I would have won’ means",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "I worked harder and won",
                        "I worked harder, yet I didn’t win",
                        "I did not work harder, yet I won",
                        "I didn’t work harder, and I didn’t win"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "If I had not opened the door, the cat ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will not jump out",
                        "would not jump out",
                        "would not have jumped out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………… . the newspaper, when the doorbell ……………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "am reading, rang",
                        "was reading, rang",
                        "had read, rang"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The opposite of the word sympathy is ................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "empathy",
                        "pity",
                        "apathy"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am going to ………………… . library.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "a",
                        "any",
                        "the"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}